BGM
Excuse me, please line up in single file in A, B, and C.
Excuse me.
First of all, you are not greeting each other at all.
When you come in, say good morning to the teacher, to everyone, and to each other.
You should definitely say this. If you can't do this, it will be the same for the rest of your life,
As an idol, it is not good if you can't say "good morning" when you are working.
Yes.
I'll put on a song with "Kalliota" in it, so let's sing it one time. Yes, I'll play something with cariotta in it. Let's play something with cariotta in it, so let's sing it once.
Yes, me.
The core of your voice is quite weak.
I want you to sing with your voice at about the same volume as your vocalization. I want you to sing with your belly and use your big breath. I want you to sing with your hands once so that you can sing with a proper understanding of what kind of expression and facial expression you should use.
I want you to understand what kind of expression you should sing and what kind of facial expression you should use.
BGMI'm only you Lead me to the spotlight I've listened to it many times, but I can't remember it well. Sorry. First of all, you can't remember it if you just listen to it. You'll never learn it.
You must sing it and learn it.
People will think that I came here to be a back-up dancer, that I came here to be in the spotlight.
We don't want to make idols who just want to make their CD debut, or who just want to perform in a box like this, or who just want to be in the spotlight.
So if you all have dreams of what you want to be, don't you have time to cry? ♪ BGM
♪ BGM Our song is ... ♪ Three, four, one, two, three, and up
We've heard so many songs.
I couldn't sing.
That's why I knew you could do it better than me
This time I could sing all the lyrics correctly
or "I can sing what I didn't sing here" or "I can sing to the rhythm
Or that you can sing to the rhythm of the song.
I could finish the dance after doing this part many times,
I think it's good to face yourself.
If you are in a hurry to see the person next to you, I think you need to face yourself.
I'm impressed that you rated Momo-chan's singing and dancing so highly.
I think you should have confidence. I think you should have confidence in yourself.
You sing really well and you're cute, so be confident and speak louder.
I've always lacked confidence in myself.
I'm good at dancing, but I couldn't remember the choreography, and I felt frustrated.
I was so frustrated that I wanted to work harder. I have to work harder. And that's the end of it. Hmm...
me
a buffalo followed by liu liu
I look forward to working with you
I had a lot of things to do
I was so frustrated
I wanted to do my best
I have to do my best
Please give me your best regardsLet's listen to Juice-Juice's new song.
Best regards